[
  {
    "prompt": "Her: I like your smile.",
    "response": "Me: I like you."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: You remind me of someone.",
    "response": "Me: Who? The pretty girl I'm taking out next week?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: That was actually clever.",
    "response": "Me: Creativity inevitably leads to attraction."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: So that's your creative talent? Pickup lines?",
    "response": "Me: You call it pickup lines. I call it modern poetry."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: Romeo definitely didn’t say that.",
    "response": "Me: He should have. No wonder he got dumped."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: They both die in the end.",
    "response": "Me: Sounds like a skill issue."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: So you’re a writer?",
    "response": "Me: No, I’m the plot twist."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: I don’t give my number to strangers.",
    "response": "Me: Lucky for you, we’re about to change that status."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: What if I’m already talking to someone?",
    "response": "Me: There’s a reason you said ‘talking’ and not ‘taken’."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: No promises though.",
    "response": "Me: Promises are for the hesitant. You seem pretty sure to me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: What is illegal?",
    "response": "Me: Clicking pictures of artwork in the meuseam"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: That's a bold statement.",
    "response": "Me: I'm a bold guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: Not sure if you can match my fun side.",
    "response": "Me: The only thing you shouldn't be sure of, is how will you stop yourself from getting addicted to all the fun we have."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Her: I appreciate your confidence\nHer: why??\nHer: What?? My eyes aren't the arist\nHer:You definetely do this often\nHer: So how do i know I'm just not another artwork?\nHer: How?\nHer: I'm speechless sir",
    "response": "Me: I appreciate you hiding your eyes in that picture.\nMe: Artworks can be revealed, the artist shouldn't.\nMe:There's a reason the eyes are called the window into the soul.\nMe:I've met a few artworks in the journey\nMe: You don't, I do.\nMe: cuz this time I'm more interested in the artist than the artwork\nMe: Well, get that fixed coz I want to hear your voice. Drop your number."
  }
]

